# Eldo Martadjaya, B.Sc.

Full-stack Web Developer



#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Nationality: Indonesia (I will need a sponsored working visa in your country). Having 10+ years of web development experience locally and abroad. I have been trained in systems design, software development, Website development, project management, systems security, maintenance. -JavaScript, Node.JS, Drupal, Wordpress, HTML5, PHP, Laravel, Magento -Web Development, Web-based Project Management, cPanel, Gulp, OOP -User Experience, Adobe Photoshop, Corporate Website, Web Content Production, GitHub, Git Bash, Web Marketing Strategy, Webmaster Services, SEO, Adobe Photoshop, E-Commerce Optimization, Social Media





+62 878 - 8826 - 2739



eldoma@gmail.com



eldoma.github.io/resume



BSD, Serpong, West of Jakarta, Indonesia

# **Education**

DEGREE NAME // MAJOR
(Almost Finished)
University of Technology,
Sydney, Master of
Computing Science,
1999-2002

DEGREE NAME // MAJOR BINUS University, Jakarta // Bachelor of Science in Information Systems, 1993-1997. GPA 3.08/4

# **Expertise**

- CMS: Drupal, Wordpress, Laravel, HTML5
- PHP, node.js
- Web Content Management
- Internet Strategy
- Web Projects
- E-Commerce Development
- Webmaster Services

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Webmaster/Developer for several client companies Self Employed | Jakarta | March 2017 - Present

- Serves as the Webmaster, Full-Stack Web Developer for several Client companies and as technology advisor.Manages the clients official websites and social media presence.
- Create new ideas and maintain campaigns, and measuring how effective those ideas are. Monitor progress using analytic tools, and answer directly to social media inquiries, all while using the client companies' voice and guidelines.
- Support the development of digital campaigns for Client companies online outreach activities by creating digital campaigns, multimedia contents, and infographics.
- Work with other Sections and Departments to coordinate their campaigns with other initiatives to fit in to the overall goals of the clients' organisation.

Websites made and maintained:

cryoisotank.com, yanwo.asia,pontidelights.com,
bestbuysworld.com,cinema-chair.com,kursisekolah.my.id,
penyet.pontidelights.com,cryogenic.cryoisotank.com,ensurgas.
cryoisotank.com, dalmacapital.com, siigas.com,
heliumindonesia.com

### Website Development Project Manager

Twinova Pty Ltd. | Suzhou, China | Oct 2014 - Jul 2017 - As Web developer to provide of multiple website projects for company and clients such as online meeting, presentation, testing and commissioning.

- Developing and collaboration with programmer to provide of static and dynamic website content for the company and use of several tools like; Photoshop, PHP/ Drupal / Wordpress coding script.
- Developing customized commercial websites on PHP & several CMS using Agile/ScrumMethodology, web design and internet content development

#### Publication

E.M (1997) Analysis & Design of System Information Inventory & Marketing at PT AMM , BINUS University Theses
E.M (2018) DOM Frontend Javascript:
ES6+Node.JS+NPM+HTML5+CSS+Webpack+NPM on Git Bash & Github link: fullstackjavascriptin.wordpress.com, Wordpress

#### Continued:

#### Web Researcher / Content Developer

Houghton Richards | Jakarta (online) | March 2017 - Present Apr 2014-Jun 2015

Translations, Website content development & Troubleshooting. Reporting directly to Chief Development Officer. Houghton Richards is Australia's Leading Domain Brokerage House.

#### Research Team Leader & Quality Assurance

PreScouter, Inc. | Jakarta (online) - Chicago | Mar 2013-Feb 2015

Marketing Analyst Research Team member and Leader, QA. Reporting directly to Marketing Analyst GM. PreScouter is a technology-enabled service that allows corporate R&D labs to outsource tasks to subject matter experts.

#### Webmaster and Support Officer at PT Surya Indotim Imex, sister company of

Geoservices (Ltd.) | Jakarta | Apr 2012-Mar 2013

Reporting to the Business Development Manager:

- Website design and development using HTML+CSS+Wordpress.
- Managing and contributing to the execution of PT SII strategy including market plan development, competitor and customer assessment, pricing and demand analysis, regulatory, political and policy assessment.
- Work with market development, product management, EPC and market communications to develop targeted product offerings.
- Provide information to business development and market communications teams to assist in the promotion of the organization's goods and/or services.
- Actively manage all customer and sales activities for the PT SII business to be the central source of all specialty and standard gas market development support for Indonesia.
- Local representative lead for external facing activities, including customer engagement, transaction execution and regulatory affairs.
- Webmaster and Product Support Developing commercial activities
- Develop and maintain relations with key personnel within the Client's organization.





FM-BINUS-AA-FPU-86/R0

#### \*\* TRANSKRIP NILAI AKHIR \*\*

No.: MIS1/1998/EN00092/U (Jenjang Pend.: STRATA 1)

Dengan ini diterangkan bahwa,

N a m a : ELBG MARTADJAJA No.Induk Mahasiswa : 0101930299 N.I.R.M : 933333716650276 Tempat & tgl.lahir : Jakarta, 11 Juli 1975

adalah mahasiswa Universitas Bina Musantara jurusan MANAJEMEN INFORMATIKA, yang telah menyelesaikan masa belajarnya dengan daftar nilai sebagai berikut :

HD.	MAMA MATA KULIAH	SKS	GRADE	KREBIT	NO.	NAMA MATA KULIAH	SKS	GRADE	KREDIT
01. 02. 03. 06. 06. 08. 09. 11. 12. 13. 15. 16. 19. 221. 223. 225. 227. 229. 331. 323. 323.	Akuntansi-1 Pengantar PDE Logika & Algoritma Etika Bahasa Inggris-1 Penrograman Cobol-1 Aljabar Linier Matematika Biskrit Manajemen Umum Akuntansi-2 Struktur Bata Metode Peranc. Program Bahasa Inggris-2 Penrograman Cobol-2 Kalkulus Basar Pengantar Sisfo ( S.I.M ) Konsep Data Base Pancasila Teknik Digital Paket Program Niaga Penrograman COBOL-3 Statistika & T. Peluang-1 Penrograman Linier Analisa Sisfo Kewiraan Pengantar Ekonomi Organisasi Komputer Komunikasi Data Bahasa Rakitan Statistika & T. Peluang-2 Pernatangan Sisfo Teknik Kompilasi Pemrograman C	515145151515151514 45N514 C1451514 CN515145151451514 514514 C151		488666864488664488666666666666666666666	36. 37. 38. 40. 41. 42. 44. 45. 46. 47. 48. 51. 52. 53. 54.	Kalkulus Lanjutan Tugas Rancang Manajemen Produksi Riset Operasional (MI) Manajemen PDE Komputer Audit Peng. Data Terdistribusi Sistem Operasi Ilmu Sosial Dasar Kepemimpinan Seminar Rekayasa Software	42422442222244224462	AAABCCAABACBBBABABL	168468462684462681268
	TOTAL KREDIT	= 148	sks			INDEX PRESTASI 3.02			

A : 85 - 100; B : 75 - 84; C : 65 - 74; D : 50 - 64; L : Lulus.

Jodel Skripsi : AMALISIS DAN PERANCANGAN SISTEM INFORMASI PEMBELIAN, PERSEDIAAN DAN PENJUALAN PADA PT AMM

Kerja Praktek di : PT. LANGGENG GITAMUSIKAL : November 1996 S/D Januari 1997 : Universitas Bina

Jakarta, 22 Desember 1998 Universitas Bina Nusantara

Ir. Th. Widia S., MM

Rektor

D02

KAMPUS SYAHDAN Universitas Bina Nusantara Jl. K.H. Syahdan No. 9, Kemanggisan - Jakarta 11480 - Telp. (021) 534 5830, 532 2160 - Fax. (021) 530 0244 KAMPUS ANGGREK Universitas Bina Nusantara Jl. Kebon Jeruk Raya - Jakarta 11480 - Telp. (021) 535 0660 Homepage BiNus : http://www.binus.ac.id/





# Sekolah Tinggi Manajemen Informatika dan Komputer (STMIK)

## **Bina Nusantara**

Jln. K.H. Syahdan - Kemanggisan, Palmerah - Jakarta Barat (11480) Fax 5300244, Telepon 5345830 - 5322160

FM-BINUS-AA-FPU-86/kV

\*\* TRANSCRIPT OF ACADEMIC RECORD \*\*

( Undergraduate Program )

This is to certify that:

N a m e : ELDO MARTADJAJA Student Number : 0101930299 Registration Number : 933333716650276 Place & Date of Birth : Jakarta, JULY 11, 1975

as finished his Undergraduate Program in Management Information System with the tollowing results:

40. SUBJECTS	CREDIT	GRADE		No.	SUBJECTS	CREDIT	GRADE	
11. Accounting-1 12. Introduction to EDP 13. Logic & Algorithms 14. Ethics 15. English-1 16. Cobot-1 Programming 16. Linear Algebra 18. Discrete Mathematics 19. General Management 19. Accounting-2 11. Data Structures 12. Program Design Method 12. English-2 14. Cobot-2 Programming 15. Calculus 16. Management Information System 17. Database Concept 18. Pancasila 19. Digital Technique 20. Package Program 21. Cobot-3 Programming 22. Statistics & Probability Theory-1 23. Linear Programming 24. Sysfo Analysis 25. Theory of National Defense 26. Introduction to Economics 27. Computer Organization 28. Bata Communication 29. Assembly Language 20. Statistics & Probability Theory-2 21. Sysfo Design 22. Compilation Technique 23. Canguage 24. Research Methodology 25. Munerical Method	2242222244224224224222422244242422	CACBBBABCCCCCBBBCCCCBABBBCCBABAABAAAAB	48866686448866644846666868666666668686	37. 38. 39. 41. 42. 43. 45. 46. 47. 51. 51. 52. 53.	System Information Project Organizational Behaviour Graph System Basic Humanity Simulation Technique Advanced Calculus Prapers Production Management Operational Research EDP Management Computer Audit Distributed Data Processing Operating System Basic Social Science Leadership Seminar Software Engineering Thesis Job Training	4242244222224224224462	AAABCCAABACBBBABABA	16 8 16 6 8 4 6 12 6 8 2 12 6 18 18
Total =	148 c	redits			Cummulative GPA = 3,02			

Total = 148 credits

Brade: 4: 85-100; B: 75-84; C: 65-74; D: 50-64; P: Passed

Title of Thesis: Analysis and Design of System Information Purchasing Inventory and Marketing at

Job Training at : PT. LANGGENG GITAMUSIKAL Period : November 1996 - January 1997

Jakarta, October 12, 1997

STMIK BINA NUSANTARA

Signed

Ir. Th. Widia S., Mh Principal

Ir. Th. Widia S., M. Principal

Attested by,